Addison Moore

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/addison-moore
Github: www.github.com/addisong12
Wobsita: http://www.addisonmoore.mo

Website: http://www.addisonmoore.me

I'm a full stack software engineer, from the San Francisco Bay Area. I'm a seasoned developer with over 7 years experience working in tech. Over the past few years I've worked as a full stack engineer on small teams where I've gained experience with a variety of tools and languages to bring applications from concept to completion.

SKILLS

Languages: Javascript, Python, Typescript, HTML, CSS, Bash, French **Frameworks and Libraries**: React, Flask, Django, React-Native, Webpack.

Backend: Node.js, Express, Python, Linux, Docker, NGINX, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Snowflake, BigQuery.

EXPERIENCE

Stratus Data / Software Engineer, Data Engineer

September 2021 - Present

- As the sole full stack engineer at stratus data, I built and launched our client facing portal. I also worked on several internal tools to improve the efficacy of our team and enabled data scientists on the team to launch client facing dashboards.
- As a data engineer, I worked with clients to build data pipelines using a variety of tools, including Airflow, DBT, Snowflake, BigQuery, SQL, Python and more. I also created APIs to transform and analyze data using natural language processing and market basket analysis.

Freelance / Full Stack Developer

MAY 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2021, SAN FRANCISCO

- Built a full stack cryptocurrency trading platform to take advantage of arbitrage opportunities between US and South Korean markets.
- Built a handful of bespoke websites for clients with custom content management systems, primarily using the MERN stack (Mongo, Express, Node, and React).

Quantum Metric / Software Engineer, Customer Success Team

JULY 2019 - July JULY, SAN FRANCISCO

- Primary engineer servicing over \$5M in contracts for brands such as Lululemon, Western Union, eBay, Stubhub, Silicon Valley Bank, and CSAA Insurance.
- Wrote clean and readable Javascript to gather analytics data and help brands measure their KPIs.
- · Worked with top brands to implement Quantum Metric on their digital platforms.

The Bosco / Product Designer, SF Operations Manager

JUNE 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2018, SAN FRANCISCO

- Lead designer on new core products including the Bosco Lite and Multicam. These products generated over \$10M in revenue during my time at The Bosco.
- Launched the Bosco's San Francisco office. Hired and managed the SF team which consisted of at least 6 operations assistants and event staff throughout my tenure.

EDUCATION

General Assembly

NOVEMBER 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019, SAN FRANCISCO

General Assembly - Web Development Immersive - 4 month full time program

California State University of Monterey Bay

AUGUST 2007 - MAY 2012, SEASIDE, CA

Bachelor's Degree - Visual and Public Art Major, Digital Art and 3D Design

Online certificates and courses:

University of Michigan: Python Data Structures

Coursera, Udemy: Meta Backend Certificate, Game Programming with C#, AGILE bootcamp

Frontend Masters: Intermediate React, Typescript, Git In-Depth, Full Stack for Frontend Engineers, Intro to containers, Networking and Streams, Complete Intro to Vue.